Man, like I said, um, tears of joy, man.
Just just feel feel feel feel feel feel
feel feel feel feel feel feel feel feel
feel feel feel feel feel feel feel b b b
b b b b b b b b b b b b b b b b b b b b
b b b b b b b b b b b b b b b b blessed
to be able to play on the field. My
brother, my blood. So feel good.
Something that we that I talked to him
about and here we go.
>> First time as teammate. I know you guys
played for the same high school and
college, but you weren't teammates
because of the age. First time as
teammates, right?
>> Yes, sir.
>> What does that mean to you?
>> Everything. Everything means the world
to me. Just like I said, being able to
play with bro. Like it mean the world.
They got me on one side, my brother on
the other side. It mean the world to me.
So, like I said, it's time to get the
word and I'm I'm blessed.
>> When did you Avon, this is Josh Kendall
with the Athletic. When did you start to
think that the Falcons would be a real
possibility in this process?
When I knew when I knew I wasn't avail
I felt it. My brother was he started
walking away so I already knew it was
coming.
>> That's great.
>> So did you you think they tipped him off
to the pick? You think he knew before
you did?
>> Like like did he know?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. He tried to act like he ain't
know. But I knew it. I know. I know,
bro. I I read through him.
Congratulations, my bot.
>> Congratulations.
>> I read through him. I'm sorry. It's a
lot going on out here. My bad.
>> Supposed to be.
>> How would you put into words what that
moment was like with you and AJ when you
get the call and you hear that you guys
are going to be teammates for the first
time for your hometown Falcons?
>> My heart dropped soon as I seen it say
Atlanta Falcon. I thought four phone
numbers come said Atlanta Falcons. My
heart look right. I look right at AJ and
told it's time. Like it's time, bro.
Feel amazing. Cheers of joy.
>> Anything else?
>> Yeah. AJ or Avian, excuse me. I'm sorry.
I'm going to do that. That That's the
first of about 15 times I'm going to do
that. I apologize. Um, how much interest
did the Falcons show in you during the
draft pro process? Did you feel like
they were taking a special interest in
you?
>> Yeah, they brought me They brought me up
down there at 30. I know they had
interest in me for sure.
>> AJ, how much time how many times did how
many times did you did you come to the
facility, you know, hang around with
your brother a little bit around the
talking organization?
>> Um, like during this process,
>> no, before that when you were maybe
maybe back when he first got into league
and stuff, did you kind of hang out with
him, come out to the facility, stuff
like that?
>> Yeah, I go I want to go watch his
practices. That's it. Just watch his
practice on the field. see him see him
do his job and go to some games. I
didn't really go through the facility
for until I won a top 30. That was my
first time in the facility.
>> Avon, we uh
>> Sorry. Go ahead, Dave.
>> Avon April Braxton Atlanta first. Just
how much was this goal of yours just to
make it to the league, you know, on your
own kind of on your own merit?
Obviously, everybody knows that you're
AJ's brother, but how much does it mean
to you to be able to kind of make your
your own mark in the league now?
You know, it mean the world to me. Um,
like just playing with my hometown, it
mean a lot. And like I said, getting
that car felt good. Y'all can hear me.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It meant the world to me
getting that call felt good. Um, it's a
blessing. Prayed for that. I prayed for
it last night.
>> Didn't know it was going to be the
Falcons, but hey, we here. I imagine
that your mom and dad were already
starting to plan how they were going to
work their weekends,
>> assuming you played somewhere else. Did
they say anything after the week about
>> Yeah, they talked about it how they
going how they gonna, you know, travel
to me, travel to AJ, but hey, they don't
got to do it no more. Ain't no
stretching no more. They don't got to
stress no more.
>> That's awesome.
>> Aon, I'm sure throughout your life you
have maybe not been in the shadow of AJ
Tro, but I'm sure referred to sometimes,
you know, oh, AJ's little brother. What
should Falcons fans know about Avon
Terrell and who you are?
>> Yeah. Um, you said what do they need to
know?
>> Yeah. Like what should they know, you
>> Yeah. That um I'm a dog. I'm a
competitor. I'm a uh coming in to be a
leader. I'm a very local a vocal leader.
And like I said, they again somebody who
very versatile that can do anything in
the second year.
Avon, are they going to uh are they
going to put your locker right next to
AJ or they going to have to keep you
guys all the way on the other side of
the locker room? Like what's your
dynamic going to be like with your
brother in there?
>> I hope they put me next to Twin. I hope
they put me next to my bro. But hey, it
is what it is. We're on the same team.
I'mma see him anyway. So, it's good.
What about the way that that he plays
and the way that he operates have you
tried to add to the way that you play
and kind of how you carry um just off
field everything? Avon,
>> can you say that again?
>> Yeah, just how much of the way that that
he plays and how he carries himself.
Have you tried to add just the way that
you play, the way you live off field and
on field for that matter?
>> Yeah. um hate the same. I feel like me
and bro move the same. You know, we talk
every day. So, the way he move out the
field, I think he moved great. You know,
I look I've been looking at him for my
whole life. So, I talk to bro every day.
And the way I move out the field is the
same way I move with with passion,
knowing how to move everything.
>> There he is.
>> Hey, AJ. Hey, what's up? Y'all straight.
>> How about you? You happy,
>> man? I'm It's crazy right now,
>> dude. That AJ,
>> I don't even know how to feel.
>> How how how proud are you of him, man?
How proud of you?
>> Another surreal moment, you feel me?
It's just been watching little bro go
for
play ball for years, you know, just
coaching him up, being the, you know,
being the the big bro. And now being
able to strap up with him, going to work
with him every day, playing on Sundays
right at the crib. Can't make it up,
man. just want to, you know, just give
all glory to God, man.
We ready, bro.
>> AJ AJ, I remember
>> it's a real dream come true.
>> AJ, I say I remember talking to you in
the locker room, Raphael Haynes from the
three-point conversion. We were talking
in the locker room about your little
brother all the time each week talking
about how proud you are of him.
>> Did you envision I asked him this, did
you envision this happening like before?
>> Of course. Of course. I I I don't I
played the I played the story in my head
a few times.
>> Yeah.
>> Um I still, you know, I ain't thinking
that happened though. You know, that's
just me being big bro. Like what if what
if what if we here though, man? It's
crazy.
>> The Atlanta Falcons tip you off at the
Falcons tip you off that they were going
to pick your brother in the draft and
what was that?
>> So had hit me. coach had hit me. I want
to say like three picks out
>> and once when you
>> I'm expecting my little bro phone to
ring. My phone ring.
You know what I'm saying? So when I when
I seen coach hit me, I ain't want to
show too much emotion cuz little bro
standing right next to me. So I tried to
but I already know what that calls for,
man. It was just
soon as he told me it was hard for me to
hold my water for a second. I was trying
to hide my emotion and everything for
like two I had to wait three picks
before I can, you know, show show some
type of love to him, man. I you know,
it's just you can't make it up. Like I
said, it's crazy.
>> Congratulations, JJ. Man, that's
awesome.
>> Like I'm living the draft again.
>> That's so cool.
>> AJ,
>> any more questions for Avon before we
let him?
>> Oh, yeah. He right here with me if y'all
got any questions.
>> Avon. Um,
>> wait, wait. You need them? You You want
them?
>> Yeah. You want them?
>> Yeah, they'd be great.
>> I'm back.
>> Um, I don't know if you thought about
this, but the idea of lining at the
corner and looking across the field and
seeing your brother, like, what do you
think what goes through your mind or
what do you think that'll be like?
>> Hey, it's go time. It's go time. It
ain't it ain't too much thinking when we
on that island. We gonna look at each
other and we gonna nod each other. It's
go time. It's time to ball.